Greetings everyone. This is Richard with
hydrogen technologytoday.com.
We're here again with the HT7 fuel cell.
This is a hydrogen only producing fuel
cell. Separates the gases on output or
actually during creation. Uh, just want
to demonstrate for you the explosion of
oxygen and the explosion of hydrogen.
Got a blue line here labeled oxygen.
This is where the oxygen's coming out.
Hydrogen's coming out this line. Going
against my better judgment. I'm going to
use the old Bick lighter trick just to
quickly demonstrate for you. Oxygen.
As you can tell, and the oxygen is set
on a
uh bleeder valve here that only releases
and you can tell there's really no
explosion from the oxygen.
Just a little
Try this again. Leave it blade in the
water here. Well, here we go.
Hardly anything out of the oxygen side.
Let's move to the hydrogen side. I'm
going to do this quickly because I don't
like the way this sounds.
And there you go. Hydrogen oxygen
separation.
HT7 hydrogen fuel cell.
[Music]